https://www.liveadmins.com/terms/

TermsTERMS OF USEYour privacy is important to LiveAdmins. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that LiveAdmins collects, and the ways in which LiveAdmins uses that personal information.Where LiveAdmins discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, LiveAdmins may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.Securing Your DataLiveAdmins will take reasonable technical and organizational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.LiveAdmins will store all the personal information you provide on its secure servers. Information relating to electronic transactions entered into via this website will be protected by encryption technology.Cross-border Data TransfersInformation that LiveAdmins collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which LiveAdmins LLC or LiveAdmins operate to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available around the world. You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.Updating this StatementLiveAdmins may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.Contact LiveAdminsIf you have any questions about this privacy policy or LiveAdmins’s treatment of your personal information, please speak with one of our chat operators. © 2020 LiveAdmins. All rights reserved.
Chat
Text
